<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeeCab</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="action_loggedUser">Logged in as</string>
    <string name="action_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">Registration</string>


    <string name="screen_name">Screen Name(the name other users see)</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hint_company_name">Company Name</string>

    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_mobile">Cell Number</string>
    <string name="hint_reg_mobile">Cell Number (i.e 0725557766)</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_pre_password">Previous Password</string>
    <string name="hint_new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="hint_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_up">Create Account</string>
    <string name="btn_log_in">Get in</string>
    <string name="btn_send_forgotten">Send</string>
    <string name="err_msg_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Enter valid email address</string>
    <string name="err_msg_password">Enter the password</string>


    <string name="tell"><u>Tell us a bit about yourself!</u> </string>

    <string name="pick_a_role">Select a style, &#8230;  well you know the drill&#8230; I hope.  </string>
    <string name="title_activity_taxi_splash">Taxi</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration_confirmation">Confirmation</string>


    <string name="msg_sit_back">Sit back &amp; Relax! while I verify your mobile number</string>
    <string name="msg_manual_otp">(Enter the OTP below in case if I fail to detect the SMS automatically)</string>
    <string name="lbl_enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="lbl_submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="btn_resend_otp">RESEND OTP</string>
    <string name="title_activity_requester">Requester</string>


    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>


    <string-array name="disease_cat">
        <item>Symptoms</item>
        <item>Care Plan</item>
        <item>Image</item>
        <item>Medication</item>

    </string-array>


    <array name="nav_drawer_start_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_launcher</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_launcher</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_launcher</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_launcher</item>

    </array>


    <string name="title_non_com">Placeholder 1</string>
    <string name="title_com">Placeholder 2</string>
    <string name="title_first_aid">Placeholder 3</string>
    <string name="title_helpline">Placeholder 4</string>

    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>@string/title_non_com</item>
        <item>@string/title_com</item>
        <item>@string/title_first_aid</item>
        <item>@string/title_helpline</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_responder">Responder</string>

    <string name="title_activity_pick__des_map">Pick a location</string>

    <string name="tap_instructions">(Drag the  marker to the location and confirm with OK)</string>
    <string name="move_the_camera">Move the camera</string>

    <!--    Permissions    -->
    <string name="permission_rationale_location">Access to the location service is required to demonstrate the \'my location\' feature, which shows your current location on the map.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">This sample requires location permission to enable the \'my location\' layer. Please try again and grant access to use the location.\nIf the permission has been permanently denied, it can be enabled from the System Settings &gt; Apps &gt; \'Google Maps API Demos\'.</string>
    <string name="permission_required_toast">Location permission is required for this demo.</string>


    <!--    Geolocation    -->
    <string name="no_geocoder_available">No geocoder available</string>

    <string name="fetch_address">Fetch address</string>

    <string name="address_found">Address found</string>

    <string name="no_address_found">Sorry, no address found</string>
    <string name="no_location_data_provided">No location data provided</string>
    <string name="service_not_available">Sorry, the service is not available</string>
    <string name="invalid_lat_long_used">Invalid latitude or longitude used</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_cab_response">ViewCabResponse</string>
    <string name="title_activity_set_route">Set Route</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_set_route2">SetRoute2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job_detail">Job Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job_responder">Responses</string>


    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>

    <string name="cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="accept">ACCEPT</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Hello from BeeCab!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Welcome to the network of cab,\n find your favorite cab companies and reliable independent drivers !</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">BeeCab is easy to use!</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Hail a cab from here the way you will do it over the phone,\n you can even haggle the fare!</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Across South Africa</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Select your pickup and destination area,\n  set the pickup time,\n  propose a fare and let the biding war begin!</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">All about YOU</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Please do not forget to complete your profile,\n Settings ->Profile </string>
    <string name="title_activity_lost_password">Lost Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_update_password">Update Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_referral_history">Referral History</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_send_referral">SendReferral</string>


    <string name="invalid_email">Invalid email address</string>
    <string name="missing_info">Missing some critical information</string>
    <string name="pwd_short">The password provided is too short (min. 6 characters)</string>
    <string name="pwd_mismatch">The password and the confirmed password do not match</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cab_caller">BeeCab</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="title_credits">BeeCab and BeeCab for Drivers</string>
    <string name="main_credits">are software developed by INQB8 Business Technologies (Pty) \n All rights reserved. More info at  </string>
    <string name="link_credits">www.inqb8.co.za - www.beecab.net - www.beecab.co.za</string>
    <string name="title_activity_credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_driver_profile_view">Driver Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_disclaimer">Disclaimer, Terms and Conditions </string>



    <string name="disclaimer">1	CONTRACTUAL RELATIONSHIP\n\n

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICES.\n
Your access and use of the Services constitutes your agreement to be bound by these Terms, which establishes a contractual relationship
        between you and BeeCab. If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not access or use the Services. These Terms expressly supersede
        prior agreements or arrangements with you. BeeCab may immediately terminate these Terms or any Services with respect to you, or generally,
        cease offering or deny access to the Services or any portion thereof, at any time for any reason.
Supplemental terms may apply to certain Services, such as policies for a particular event, activity or promotion, and such supplemental terms will be
        disclosed to you in connection with the applicable Services. Supplemental terms are in addition to, and shall be deemed a part of, the Terms
        for the purposes of the applicable Services. Supplemental terms shall prevail over these Terms in the event of a conflict with respect to the
        applicable Services.
BeeCab may amend the Terms related to the Services from time to time. Amendments will be effective upon BeeCab’s posting of such updated Terms at this
        location or the amended policies or supplemental terms on the applicable Service. Your continued access or use of the Services after such
        posting constitutes your consent to be bound by the Terms, as amended.\n\n

2	THE SERVICES\n\n

The Services constitute a technology platform that enables users of BeeCab’s mobile applications or websites provided as part of the Services
        (each, an “Application”) to arrange and schedule transportation and/or logistics services with independent third party providers of
        such services, including independent third party transportation providers and independent third party logistics providers under agreement
        with BeeCab or certain of BeeCab’s affiliates (“Third Party Providers”). Unless otherwise agreed by BeeCab in a separate written agreement
        with you, the Services are made available solely for your personal, noncommercial use. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT BEECAB DOES NOT PROVIDE
        TRANSPORTATION OR LOGISTICS SERVICES OR FUNCTION AS A TRANSPORTATION CARRIER AND THAT ALL SUCH TRANSPORTATION OR LOGISTICS SERVICES ARE PROVIDED
        BY INDEPENDENT THIRD PARTY CONTRACTORS WHO ARE NOT EMPLOYED BY BEECAB OR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES.\n
2.1	License.\n
Subject to your compliance with these Terms, BeeCab grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-sub licensable, revocable, non-transferrable
        license to: (i) access and use the Applications on your personal device solely in connection with your use of the Services; and (ii)
        access and use any content, information and related materials that may be made available through the Services, in each case solely for your
        personal, noncommercial use. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by BeeCab and BeeCab’s licensors.\n
2.2	Restrictions.\n
You may not: (i) remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notices from any portion of the Services; (ii) reproduce, modify, prepare derivative works based upon, distribute, license, lease, sell, resell, transfer, publicly display, publicly perform, transmit, or otherwise exploit the Services except as expressly permitted by BeeCab; (iii) decompile, reverse engineer or disassemble the Services except as may be permitted by applicable law; (iv) link to, mirror or frame any portion of the Services; (v) cause or launch any programs or scripts for the purpose of scraping, indexing, surveying, or otherwise data mining any portion of the Services or unduly burdening or hindering the operation and/or functionality of any aspect of the Services; or (vi) attempt to gain unauthorized access to or impair any aspect of the Services or its related systems or networks.
2.3	Third Party Services and Content.\n
The Services may be made available or accessed in connection with third party services and content (including advertising) that BeeCab does not control. You acknowledge that different terms of use and privacy policies may apply to your use of such third party services and content. BeeCab does not endorse such third party services and content and in no event shall BeeCab be responsible or liable for any products or services of such third party providers. Additionally, Apple Inc., Google, Inc., Microsoft Corporation or BlackBerry Limited and/or their applicable international subsidiaries and affiliates will be third-party beneficiaries to this contract if you access the Services using Applications developed for Apple iOS, Android, Microsoft Windows, or Blackberry-powered mobile devices, respectively. These third party beneficiaries are not parties to this contract and are not responsible for the provision or support of the Services in any manner. Your access to the Services using these devices is subject to terms set forth in the applicable third party beneficiary’s terms of service.
2.4	Ownership.\n
The Services and all rights therein are and shall remain BeeCab’s property or the property of BeeCab’s licensors. \n\n

3	YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES\n\n

3.1	User Accounts.\n
In order to use most aspects of the Services, you must register for and maintain an active personal user Services account (“Account”). You must be at
        least 18 years of age, or the age of legal majority in your jurisdiction (if different than 18), to obtain an Account. Account registration
        requires you to submit to BeeCab certain personal information, such as your name, address, mobile phone number, and age, as well as at least
        one valid payment method (either a credit card or accepted payment partner). You agree to maintain accurate, complete, and up-to-date
        information in your Account. Your failure to maintain accurate, complete, and up-to-date Account information, including having an invalid or
        expired payment method on file, may result in your inability to access and use the Services or BeeCab’s termination of these Terms with you.
        You are responsible for all activity that occurs under your Account, and you agree to maintain the security and secrecy of your Account
        username and password at all times. Unless otherwise permitted by BeeCab in writing, you may only possess one Account.\n
3.2	User Requirements and Conduct.\n
The Service is not available for use by persons under the age of 18. You may not authorize third parties to use your Account, and you may not allow
        persons under the age of 18 to receive transportation or logistics services from Third Party Providers unless they are accompanied by you.
        You may not assign or otherwise transfer your Account to any other person or entity. You agree to comply with all applicable laws when using
        the Services, and you may only use the Services for lawful purposes (e.g., no transport of unlawful or hazardous materials). You will not,
        in your use of the Services, cause nuisance, annoyance, inconvenience, or property damage, whether to the Third Party Provider or any other party.\n\n

3.3	User Provided Content.\n
BeeCab may, in BeeCab’s sole discretion, permit you from time to time to submit, upload, publish or otherwise make available to BeeCab through the Services textual, audio, and/or visual content and information, including commentary and feedback related to the Services, Any User Content provided by you remains your property. However, by providing User Content to BeeCab, you grant BeeCab a worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, transferrable, royalty-free license, with the right to sublicense, to use, copy, modify, create derivative works of, distribute, publicly display, publicly perform, and otherwise exploit in any manner such User Content in all formats and distribution channels now known or hereafter devised (including in connection with the Services and BeeCab’s business and on third-party sites and services), without further notice to or consent from you, and without the requirement of payment to you or any other person or entity.
You represent and warrant that: (i) you either are the sole and exclusive owner of all User Content or you have all rights, licenses, consents and releases necessary to grant BeeCab the license to the User Content as set forth above; and (ii) neither the User Content nor your submission, uploading, publishing or otherwise making available of such User Content nor BeeCab’s use of the User Content as permitted herein will infringe, misappropriate or violate a third party’s intellectual property or proprietary rights, or rights of publicity or privacy, or result in the violation of any applicable law or regulation.
You agree to not provide User Content that is defamatory, libelous, hateful, violent, obscene, pornographic, unlawful, or otherwise offensive, as determined by BeeCab in its sole discretion, whether or not such material may
        be protected by law. BeeCab may, but shall not be obligated to, review, monitor, or remove User Content, at BeeCab’s sole discretion and at
        any time and for any reason, without notice to you.\n
3.4	Network Access and Devices.\n
You are responsible for obtaining the data network access necessary to use the Services. Your mobile network’s data and messaging rates and fees may apply if you access or use the Services from a wireless-enabled device and you shall be responsible for such rates and fees. You are responsible for acquiring and updating compatible hardware or devices necessary to access and use the Services and Applications and any updates thereto. BeeCab does not guarantee that the Services, or any portion thereof, will function on any particular hardware or devices. In addition, the Services may be subject to malfunctions and delays inherent in the use of the Internet and electronic communications.
\n\n
4	PAYMENT\n\n

You understand that use of the Services may result in charges to you for the services or goods you receive from a Third Party Provider (“Charges ”). All Charges are due immediately and payment must be made to the driver.
You may elect to cancel your request for services or goods from a Third Party Provider at any time prior to such Third Party Provider’s arrival at no cost.
You understand and agree that, while you are free to provide additional payment as a gratuity to any Third Party Provider who provides you with services or goods obtained through the Service, you are under no obligation to do so. Gratuities are voluntary. After you have received services or goods obtained through the Service, you will have the opportunity to rate your experience.
\n\n
5	DISCLAIMERS; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY; INDEMNITY\n\n

5.1	DISCLAIMER.\n
THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE.” BEECAB DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, NOT EXPRESSLY
        SET OUT IN THESE TERMS, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN ADDITION,
        BEECAB MAKES NO REPRESENTATION, WARRANTY, OR GUARANTEE REGARDING THE RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, QUALITY, SUITABILITY OR AVAILABILITY OF THE
        SERVICES OR ANY SERVICES OR GOODS REQUESTED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICES, OR THAT THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE.
        BEECAB DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE QUALITY, SUITABILITY, SAFETY OR ABILITY OF THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS. YOU AGREE THAT THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF
        YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, AND ANY SERVICE OR GOOD REQUESTED IN CONNECTION THEREWITH, REMAINS SOLELY WITH YOU, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED
        UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.\n
5.2	LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.\n
BEECAB SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE RELATED TO, IN CONNECTION WITH, OR OTHERWISE RESULTING FROM ANY USE OF THE SERVICES, EVEN IF BEECAB HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BEECAB SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, LIABILITY OR LOSSES ARISING OUT OF: (i) YOUR USE OF OR RELIANCE ON THE SERVICES OR YOUR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICES; OR (ii) ANY TRANSACTION OR RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU AND ANY THIRD PARTY PROVIDER, EVEN IF BEECAB HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BEECAB SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DELAY OR FAILURE IN PERFORMANCE RESULTING FROM CAUSES BEYOND BEECAB’S REASONABLE CONTROL.
BEECAB’S SERVICES MAY BE USED BY YOU TO REQUEST AND SCHEDULE TRANSPORTATION, GOODS OR LOGISTICS SERVICES WITH THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS, BUT YOU AGREE THAT BEECAB HAS NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO YOU RELATED TO ANY TRANSPORTATION, GOODS OR LOGISTICS SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS OTHER THAN AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THESE TERMS.
THE LIMITATIONS AND DISCLAIMER IN THIS SECTION 5 DO NOT PURPORT TO LIMIT LIABILITY OR ALTER YOUR RIGHTS AS A CONSUMER THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED UNDER
        APPLICABLE LAW.\n
5.3	Indemnity.\n
You agree to indemnify and hold BeeCab and its officers, directors, employees and agents harmless from any and all claims, demands, losses, liabilities, and expenses (including attorneys’ fees) arising out of or in connection with: (i) your use of the Services or services or goods obtained through your use of the Services; (ii) your breach or violation of any of these Terms; (iii) BeeCab’s use of your User Content; or (iv) your violation of the rights of any third party, including Third Party Providers.
6	GOVERNING LAW; ARBITRATION\n\n

Except as otherwise set forth in these Terms, these Terms shall be exclusively governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of South Africa. \n
6.1	Notice.\n
BeeCab may give notice by means of a general notice on the Services, electronic mail to your email address in your Account, or by written communication
        sent to your address as set forth in your Account. \n
6.2	General.\n
You may not assign or transfer these Terms in whole or in part without BeeCab’s prior written approval. You give your approval to BeeCab for it to assign or transfer these Terms in whole or in part, including to: (i) a subsidiary or affiliate; (ii) an acquirer of BeeCab’s equity, business or assets; or (iii) a successor by merger. No joint venture, partnership, employment or agency relationship exists between you, BeeCab or any Third Party Provider as a result of the contract between you and BeeCab or use of the Services.
If any provision of these Terms is held to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable, in whole or in part, under any law, such provision or part thereof shall to that extent be deemed not to form part of these Terms but the legality, validity, and enforceability of the other provisions of these Terms shall not be affected. In that event, the parties shall replace the illegal, invalid or unenforceable provision or part thereof with a provision or part thereof that is legal, valid and enforceable and that has, to the greatest extent possible, a similar effect as the illegal, invalid or unenforceable provision or part thereof, given the contents and purpose of these Terms. These Terms constitute the entire agreement and understanding between the parties with respect to its subject matter and replace and supersede all prior or contemporaneous agreements or undertakings regarding such subject matter. In these Terms, the words "including" and "include" mean "including, but not limited to."


</string>

</resources>
